<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WikiClover</string>
    <string name="blackBulls">Like the other eight squads, Black Bull follows the orders of the Magic Emperor and will act according to his requests. All squads, including the Black Bull, perform missions all around the Clover Kingdom whether they are official or unofficial.Additionally, the Magic Emperor rewards stars to squads whenever they have performed excellently on their respective missions. The Black Bulls had gathered -31 stars due to destructive behavior that caused their performance to be more harmful than the threat of the missions themselves. However, due to Asta arrival in the squad and the recent mission successes, they no longer have any black stars.[6] Additionally, while officially only coming in second during the Star Awards Festival, they would have beat Golden Dawns 125-star count by 7, had they not been starting in the negative.The squad also has a tradition of performing an initiation ceremony when dealing with their new members. This ceremony has been regarded by many of the members as unofficial but exists to measure the quality of its new recruits.[7] Upon the end of the ceremony, a senior member usually bestows the new member with the squads official robe as proof of membership.[8]</string>
    <string name="greenMantis">Like the other eight squads, the Crimson Lion follows the orders of the Magic Emperor and will act according to his requests.It is one of the most prominent and successful squads, usually ranking first or second; however, they have recently dropped to fifth</string>
    <string name="goldenDawn">The squad is currently regarded as the best among the nine squads of the order of the Magic Knights. According to the stars they have collected given by the Magic Emperor fortheir excellent performance from completing missions, the Golden Dawn sits at the top of the chart with 125 stars, up from 75 stars. The squads uniforms are similar in design to the clothes wornby Lemiel Silvamillion Clover, the first Magic Emperor.</string>
    <string name="orcas">Al igual que los otros ocho escuadrones, Orca Púrpura sigue las órdenes del Rey Mago y actuará de acuerdo a sus peticiones.Miembros Orca Púrpura es liderado por un capitán con autoridad sobre los miembros del escuadrón. </string>
    <string name="ciervos">Like the other eight squads, Azure Deer follows the orders of the Wizard King and will act according to his requests. All squads, including the Azure Deer, perform missions all around the Clover Kingdom whether they are official or unofficial.Additionally, the Wizard King rewards stars to squads whenever they have performed excellently on their respective missions. The Azure Deer has gathered 25 stars for their excellent missions they ve completed Members Azure Deer is led by a captain with authority over the members of the squad who has the duty to delegate missions, relay messages received from the Wizard King, and distribute the members salaries. Additionally, the captain decides whether a mage is to be accepted into the ranks of the squad. The decision can be made after the captain has seen the potential members ability during the exam or out of sheer compassion. </string>
    <string name="crimson">Like the other eight squads, the Crimson Lion follows the orders of the Magic Emperor and will act according to his requests.It is one of the most prominent and successful squads, usually ranking first or second;[2] however, they have recently dropped to fifth</string>
    <string name="bluerose">The Blue Roses headquarters is a mansion-like structure in an unknown region of the Clover Kingdom. Inside, there is a courtyard with one section lowered. At its center is a round water fountain and facing it is a raised platform. This section is lined with rosebushes.</string>
    <string name="eagles">Like the other eight squads, Silver Eagle follows the orders of the Wizard King and will act according to his requests. All squads, including the Silver Eagle, perform missions all around the Clover Kingdom whether they are official or unofficial.Additionally, the Wizard King rewards stars to squads whenever they have performed excellently on their respective missions. The Silver Eagle has gathered 68 stars for their excellent missions they ve completed. It is one of the most prominent and successful squads, usually ranking first or second along with the Crimson Lion squad.Members Silver Eagle is led by a captain with authority over the members of the squad who has the duty to delegate missions, relay messages received from the Wizard King, and distribute the members salaries. Additionally, the captain decides whether a mage is to be accepted into the ranks of the squad. The decision can be made after the captain has seen the potential members ability during the exam or out of sheer compassion, however the squad is based on royals and elite nobles who were the most desired among the Magic Knights and is said to be the strongest mages among the organization. </string>
</resources>
